A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Tech Chapter of Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS), 1992-2014
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the Virginia Tech Chapter of Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS), 1992-2014
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 31/2/23
0.9 Cubic Feet; 2 boxes
This collection contains the records of Randolph Grayson on the Virginia Tech student chapter of Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS), dating from 1992 through 2014. Materials include scrapbooks, photographs, correspondence, and general information about the organization, divided into five series.
Grayson, Randolph, Dr.
Minorities in Agriculture Natural Resources and Related Sciences. Virginia Tech Chapter
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The collection was transferred to Special Collections in 2019.
Administrative History
Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS) is a national, non-profit organization that promotes and empowers diverse students in agriculture, natural resources, and related sciences. They provide opportunities for different jobs, internships, and research. The organization was founded at Michigan State University in 1984.
Scope and Content
This collection contains the records of Randolph Grayson on the Virginia Tech student chapter of Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS), dating from 1992 through 2014. Materials include scrapbooks, photographs, correspondence, and general information about the organization, divided into five series.
Series I: Scrapbooks comprises two scrapbooks from 1995 to 2001 with photographs of students participating in various talks and MANRRS meetings.
Series II: General MANRRS Information consists of information packets that students might have received, chapter rosters, and meeting minutes.
Series III: Correspondence includes emails to MANRRS, articles about the organization, and a letter to MANRRS from the Women Resource Center.
In Series IV: MANRRS Leadership, there is a packet about the student budget board and tips for how the chapter should be run, as well as a "chapter advisor's handbook" for MANRRS from 2009.
The last series, Series V: Photographs, contains various photographs of students involved in MANRRS from 1996 to 2000, including photos of students participating in various activities, photos of a National MANRRS meeting in 1997, old photo labels, and a photo collage.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into five series by type.
Series I: Scrapbooks, 1995-2001
Series II: General MANRRS Information, 1992-2014, undated
Series III: Correspondence, 2000, 2011-2013, undated
Series IV: MANRRS Leadership, 2007-2009, undated
Series V: MANRRS Photographs, 1996-2000, undated
Index Terms
Subjects:
Diversity in higher education; Photographs; University History; University Archives
Organizations:
Minorities in Agriculture Natural Resources and Related Sciences. Virginia Tech Chapter; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Contents List
- Series I: Scrapbooks, 1995-2001
  - MANRRS Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Box 1)
  - MANRRS Scrapbook, 1998-2001 (Box 1)
- Series II: General MANRRS Information, 1992-2014, undated
  - MANRRS Overview, 1992, 2001, 2007, 2008, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - MANRRS, 2010-2012, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series III: Correspondence, 2000, 2011-2013, undated
  - MANRRS Articles/Correspondence, 2011-2013, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letter from the Women's Resource Center, 2000-01-26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Series IV: MANRRS Leadership, 2007-2009, undated
  - MANRRS Leadership Information, 2007-2009, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Advisor's Handbook, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series V: MANRRS Photographs, 1996-2000, undated
  - Various MANRRS Photos, 1996-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photos of National MANRRS Meeting, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MANRRS Photos, 1998-1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - MANRRS Photo Labels, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - MANRRS Photo Collage, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)